Jolaosho Abdulbateen

I am experienced in the Design Fields as a Graphics and front-end designer. Having worked with different companies, as a freelancer and with other institutions, I can boldly work productively on any task I see within my capabilities. I tend to see through events and problems making me a great problem solver. I believe I don't know everything but I can learn anything

| Experience | |
|---|-------------------------------|
| Graphic Designer TechieHealth Pharmacy | May 2021 - Present |
| Upgraded existing brand designs. Created Ui designs for front-end developers created E-Flyers for posts | |
| Graphic Designer TechLava Softwares, Abeokuta, Ogun (Nigeria) | Sep 2020 - Present |
| Created brand identity design elements.Seldomly create UI designs. | |
| Graphic Designer LifeSynca (Personal brand), Abeokuta, Ogun (Nigeria) | |
| Graphic Designer PrimAgric, Abeokuta, Ogun (Nigeria) | Oct 2019 - Jan 2021 |
| Working on producing Weekly Flies Upraded existing brand design Elements Supervised other designers on creating Flyer templates | |
| Skills & Specialization | |
| brand design, InkScape, Graphics Design, PhotoShop, UI design., Front-end design | |
| Education | |
| Federal University of Agriculture Abeokuta Mechatronics Engineering | Sep 2019 - Presently Enrolled |
| Websites | |
| www.linkedin.com/in/bataino | |